Kevin Tang

Email: kevwutang@yahoo.com

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS

Performance-driven professional offering 3 years of experience in information technology, and over 10 years in customer service. Courteous and prompt Field Service Technician with superior customer service skills. Excellent at time management and organization, even working under pressure while juggling multiple tasks. Strong qualifications developed over comprehensive experience with focus on information management, IT support services, and network administration. I am currently studying to acquire a certification in ITIL where I also continue to work on various projects. This is an intensive course that will further prepare me for a career in the technology field and more.

SKILLS AND PROFICIENCIES

- Security Clearance: Top Secret SCI
- Customer service experiences
- Remedy
- VPN
- Desktop Anywhere
- Windows XP, Vista, 7, 8, 10
- Microsoft Office suites 2003/2007/2010/2013
- Hard drives, monitors, printers, scanners and video equipment
- Help Desk Support
- Desktop/Network Administration

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Client Services Technician

618 Air Communication Squadron Scott AFB, 62225, IL

July 2019 - Present

- Shift lead; oversaw 72 weapon system & solved 291 cyber-attacks.
- Delivers 24/7 global cyber capes; expedites incident response on specialized networks, hardware & software.
- Provides Tier II tech support; maintains \$3.2M specialized comm equipment & services enabling C2 for 900 AOC users & flight planners.
- Oversees multi-directorate efforts to integrate next-gen tech; drives theater-wide C4I capes for AMC, 18 AF & 618 AOC.
- Articulates real-time C2 system & network status to HQ AMC/AOC senior

leaders, senior controllers, and flight managers ISO 1.1K aircrafts.

- Aided AOC's alt-site system overhaul; configured 28 HDDs/upgraded flight planning software; readied controller ops COOP cape.
- Organized emergency response; restored Intel Dir C4I capes; aided senior leaders' access for global contingency coordinate.
- Expedited Exec travel flight plan system upgrades; prepped/deployed 8 C2 system.
- ID'd 1K vulnerable system, patched 10K exploits; fortified AOC's 800TB cyber-attack surface.
- Orchestrated PC lab equipment reorganizes; DRMO'd 1K IT assets/prepared salvage depot; repurposed \$100K hardware assets
- Advanced AOC remote ops unit; configured 80 mobile msn system, aced security manager directive/paved \$183K alt-site.
- Managed 20 members holiday ops; organized 3 shifts & sustained 24/7 support, maxed manning efficiency/cyber oversight.
- Executed \$103M AOC relocation project; moved/prepared 5K C2 system.
- Fueled mobile flight plan sys deployment; delivered AOC C2 agility/ops anywhere cape.

Shift Lead

Starbucks *Encinitas*, 92024, CA

March 2014 - July 2018

Shift Lead 2017

- Balancing cash register and making deposits
- Ordering supplies and assisting with unloading truck deliveries
- Training and onboarding new partners
- Ensuring food safety procedures are being always followed
- Working to address partners and customer concerns.

Barista Trainer 2016

- Worked with team in a drive thru to produce and sell quality consistent coffee through relationship development with customers
- Acted on educational opportunity and utilized upsell practices
- Identified community preference and needs; maintained excellent customer service standards while encouraging coworkers
- Properly trained new partners to meet company standard and promote corporate value

Barista 2014

- Gives excellent and friendly customer service
- Accurate cash handling and operation of POS system
- Stocking out pastries, cookies, etc. for sale; restocking products as necessary
- Provides high-level of coffee service during busy hours, includes making a variety of espresso

and non-espresso drinks

• Up keeping our high cleanliness standards, maintaining a clean and organized workstation

Courtesy Clerk

Ralphs Grocery Company *Encinitas*, 92024, CA

June 2004 – August 2006

- Assists cashier bagging grocery items as customers checking out
- Loads purchased items into carts and help customers carry out items to their automobiles
- Responsible for collecting grocery items not purchased and delivering items back to the stock clerks
- Assist with collecting and returning carts to the store from outside

EDUCATION

- California State of San Marcos
 - Obtained B.S. Business Management & Organization.
- Palomar Community College
 - o Obtained credits for transfer.
- La Costa Canyon High School
 - o Obtained Diploma/GED.
- CompTIA Security +